securepctuneup.com 2017-06-22

# Privacy Policy- Secure PC Tuneup

## General

SecurePCTuneup.com is strongly committed to protecting your privacy and providing a safe online experience for all of our users and registered customers, while offering the highest quality products and services to them. We may gather certain types of information about and from you to fulfill your request and serve your needs better. We feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions covering the collection and use of this information. This privacy statement discloses what information we may gather, how we may use it and how to correct or change it. Please read the "Privacy Policy" completely, as well as our “Terms and Conditions” for use of information we may gather. Should you have any questions in this regard, feel free to contact us.

### What Information we may collect about you?

You can visit our website, read product descriptions and other materials, and check on offerings without giving us any personally identifiable information. Since we provide our customers and newsletter subscribers with the most efficient and enhanced personalized service, we may request information about you under occasional circumstances. For your convenience and to serve you better, a customer account includes all the collected personal information we may have; however, you can update or correct your contact information or change your preferences about receiving newsletter and other information from us.

We collect personally identifiable information; such as name, mailing address and e-mail address when you register one of our products or place an order (see the section below for more information on placing orders). Website visitors may register to receive our newsletter by submitting their name and e-mail address.

#### Placing Orders

If you wish to place an order for our products, you can generally enter the requisite details that may be required to fill your order (full name, address, phone number, ship-to name and address etc.). In addition, collection of further information such as your credit card number and credit card expiration date is dependent on method of payment.

#### Use of Programs

In connection with the installation and use of SPCT applications we may collect certain information concerning the use of applications or the services, including certain personal data and information about your PC. This may include information about your: installed software and hardware, your IP address, your operating system, your version of installed SPCT applications including product keys, and about the use of individual functions of SPCT applications including the relevant times. Some applications are dependant on use of WebServices for their functioning and they do send such relevant data with each use.

##### Purpose of Data Collection

Applications and services can use the aforementioned information to send product recommendations, product updates, and important customer service notifications directly to your computer. Furthermore, the data is used for the purposes of product and market analysis which enables us to improve individual products and the range of products and services.

##### Sharing of Data with Third Party

The aforementioned data may be shared with third party vendors and partners and it will be governed by their privacy policy, which will be provided to you when you accept any offer by them.

Consent for the Collection, Storage, Use and Distribution of the Data, you hereby agree to the collection and use of the such information or data by SPCT.

### What we may do with the Information we collect?

We use information you provide to fulfill your request and improve our products and services. We may use personal information to display or send personalized content to our website visitors as well as to send newsletter, product features, promotional material, special offers and other updates to our customers and newsletter subscribers. A subscriber may, at any time, opt out of receiving such information. We also use collected information to evaluate and administer our products and services, resolve customers’ issues like responding to any problems that may arise such as product delivery failures, difficulties in navigating our sites or accessing certain features, as well as to gauge user trends to determine what products are most popular with users.

We allow users of our website to email us their queries. We do not retain any email address (unless you are a member who already has voluntarily provided your email address) of either the sender or recipient of such e-mail or links after they are sent.

### How we may share Personal Information?

###### Credit Card Companies

###### Payment Gateways

We may share your personal information with the parties described below:

##### Credit Card Companies :

As in any transaction, your credit card company will have all relevant information about the name of the products purchased, date and total cost, etc. SPCT will not otherwise provide any personal data to your credit card company.

##### Payment Gateways :

Credit card numbers are only shared with our partners with whom you place an online order. They process the billing of such products on our behalf. Rest assured that we and our payment gateways follow careful procedures to safeguard credit card data in connection with your transactions.

##### Important Note :

We reserve the right to use or disclose any information without notice or consent as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request; to conduct investigations of consumer complaints or possible breaches of law; to protect the integrity of our site and our property; to protect the safety of our visitors or others; to fulfill your requests; or to cooperate in any legal investigation.

### How do we use cookies?

Your Web browser offers so-called "cookies" which, if you allow their use, store small amounts of data on your computer when you visit a website. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you and therefore cannot be used to identify your personal details. Cookies assist us in ascertaining which of our products you like best. Cookies also enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser settings. Our website is viewable even if you disable the cookie function on your browser.

##### Links

SecurePCTuneup.com may offer links to or from websites it controls to other sites within the SPCT family. We offer links to some renowned websites that review and rate our products and market them so that you can be conversant on authenticity of products performance.

##### Changes to Privacy Policy

We will occasionally update the "Privacy Policy" as necessary to protect you and to comply with a changing environment. We recommend that you check the policy when you visit our site to be sure you are aware of and understand the prevailing policy. If we make material changes to this policy we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. We will not make material changes in how we may handle any of your previously collected personal information that have retroactive effect unless legally required to do so, and we will e-mail registered customers and newsletter subscribers information on material changes to this policy.

##### Contact Information

Should you have further queries, please e-mail us at support@jawego.com or you can drop a mail at:

**SecurePCTuneup.com**   
16780 Bryant Road #9   
Lake Oswego, Oregon, 97035
